SHOCKING: What Happened After I Slept With A Prostitute!!!
This young man came to The SCOAN from Kaduna in northern Nigeria with a problem of permanent erection,
diagnosed in his medical report from the Lagos State Government Hospital as priapism.
Mister Victor Kachiro, although just 24 years of age, has been suffering with this problem for several months.
He stands still raising his t-shirt, then turns slowly to his left-hand side to show the obvious bulge in his trousers.
Gently sliding his baggy trousers down, the painful permanent erection is clear to see.
HEALING TIME
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministers prayer and healing under the control of the Spirit of God
to people with various afflictions, in need of divine mercy.
Please, help my son, man of God!
He met a prostitute and has been having a permanent erection.
Please, man of God, help my son.
Help my son, nam of God!
In the Name of Jesus Christ, Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for Victor Kachiro
and the cause of the problem of permanent erection is destroyed by the power of the Holy Ghost.
He falls to the floor under the Spirit of God's delivering influence, declared free, in Jesus' name.
He rises to his feet to thank Jesus Christ - his healer.
Thank You, Jesus, I am free!
Thank You, Jesus, my son is free!
Some time later, Mr Victor Kachiro returned to The SCOAN to testify of what the Lord Jesus Christ
has done in his life after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Let's watch!
BEFORE | AFTER
As you can see now, I am healed.
I can touch it; I can feel it.
I don’t feel any pain anymore.
I couldn’t do this before but now, I can do it.
Thank You, Jesus!
The erection is gone; everything is gone.
I am healed – totally healed!
Thank You, Jesus!
I am healed!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Victor Kachiro
The woman standing next to me is my mum - her name is Rebeca Kachiro.
This is my dad - mister Kachiro.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was a permanent erection.
I had been suffering from this problem since December, 2016 when I went out with my friends.
We did all sorts of bad things.
That was what led to the permanent erection.
This is how it all started: my friends and I would go out and take all sorts of things,
like drinking beer and smoking cigarettes.
Then, we would look for prostitute and sleep with them.
The next day after sleeping with a prostitute, I discovered that my penis was erect
and was unable to go down; I was in so much pain.
After that...
So, just to be clear brother - immediately after you met with this prostitute, under the influence of alcohol,
smoking, the following morning your erection was permanent and it refused to go down
and was extremely painful.
Yes.
Then, I was taken to hospital where the doctor told me that I had to be operated on.
After the doctor told me that I was to be operated...
At that time, I was in pain and had no choice.
I laid on the bed waiting for them to carry out their procedures.
When my mum came, I told her what the doctor had said.
My mum said no, that I couldn’t be operated on as she had faith that God could do it for me.
I'm sorry brother; when the doctors booked you for an operation, what did they say would happen to you
after the operation, as a consequence of doing that operation?
They said that I might become impotent.
So, the doctors told you that there was a high risk of you becoming impotent, as a result of this operation,
but because of the pain you were going through, you agreed to it and you were booked for the operation,
when your mum came and met you at the hospital?
Yes.
So, after that...
They even convinced me that I had the right to decide on my own whether or not to be operated on.
I then told them that since my mum was there, I would go with what she advised.
I would go anywhere my mum took me to.
That day, they even wrote notes about us with a red pen instead of a blue one -
because they were angry – I don’t know why.
We went home and the next day, we came to Lagos.
On the 20th of December, we came to The SCOAN.
We want to understand; when you came to The SCOAN, you were in this very critical situation, in a lot of pain,
and Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for you.
Can you describe to us what happened when he prayed for you?
When he prayed for me, I felt so happy and I am relieved.
Everything in normal.
I feel like a newborn baby.
OK.
So, we saw when he prayed for you, you actually fell to the ground.
Can you describe what was happening in your body at that moment?
When he laid his hand on me, firstly, it felt like there was a flash of light on my eyes,
after which, I fell on the ground.
While on the ground, I didn't know what was happening.
I regained full consciousness and found that everything was back to normal!
- Praise the Lord!
- Amen!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So, you mean to say brother that at that moment the severe, intense pain left and you were relieved?
And tell us what happened after the prayer.
After the prayer and regaining full consciousness, I felt normal.
I went back home and everything was back to normal.
I no longer did the things I used to do.
I returned fully to my normal self.
You mean to say that the pain left and then you realised that the erection started reducing
and finally it returned completely to normal, just a few days after that touch from Jesus Christ?
Yes.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
Brother, it has been several months since then; just tell us - does it mean that for this whole period
you have been living a normal life, freely, without having that pain or permanent erection?
Yes.
Everything is...
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
To the glory of God; can you just show us, touch the area, so we can see for ourselves the fact
that everything is normal now?
You can see it here.
Everything is back to normal.
I can jump and bend down now.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We can see people laughing but obviously, if you were in his position, you would understand the amount of pain
he suffered when he was injured,
even to the extent that doctors actually booked him for an operation because of that situation.
To the glory of God - he is completely free now.
Brother, what do you want to advise viewers around the world, especially young people,
since you acknowledged that it was as a result of influence of bad friends, going out to meet prostitutes,
smoking and drinking, that led you to this predicament?
What is your advice to the young people?
The advice that I want to give to young people is to stay away from bad friends and prostitutes
because they will make your life miserable.
Always keep good friends, who will lead you to the right way,
not bad friends who will lead you to the wrong way
because they will not help you in your future; they cannot help matters.
Always follow the Scripture and keep it in your heart.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
That is an advice born of life experience.
We believe that our brothers and sisters around the world are listening what our brother has to say.
Let's quickly hear a word from your mum.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
Children of God; Emmanuel!
I am Mrs Rebecca Kachiro.
I am from Kaduna State.
That is my lovely husband there,
and this is my son.
I am a mother of six - this is my fourth born.
It all happened...
He lives quite a distance away from us.
I had received a phone call that he was sick.
It was as if they were trying to hide it from me; they didn’t want me to know the actual problem.
Because of the pain he was in, he had agreed to be operated upon.
To God be the glory, it was a divine arrangement.
He was supposed to be taken to theatre that fateful day at 9am.
But I left Kaduna at 10:30am.
They did not take him to theatre before I arrived.
When I arrived, I told them that no, this boy would not be operated on.
They asked me why and I replied that my faith was not in the hospital.
To God be the glory, I overheard the doctors discussing among themselves
that they would operate on him and everything would go well
but that there was the risk that he would become impotent.
I then told my husband what the doctors had said.
He asked, "Since the boy is in pain, what do we do?"
I said no, that God would do something.
I pleaded; they took me to the general manager of the hospital to convince me
that my boy should undergo the operation.
I told them that my faith was not in the hospital,
that they should allow me to take the boy to church.
So, that was how in the end, God won the battle for me.
They took him to theatre to force him to be operated on.
I saw him coming out saying, "Madam, since you..."...
They gave me a document and asked me to sign it.
I insisted on reading the wording before I signed it.
It stated that I would take full responsibility in the event that anything happened to him.
I told them that I would come back to that hospital with a testimony.
Praise the Lord!
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
We thank God for our mother's faith.
She realised that this problem was not just a natural problem but a spiritual one.
We all know that doctors treat but Jesus Christ cures.
Doctors are playing a wonderful role in helping many people but our mother realised that the case of her son
was not a natural situation but a spiritual situation, that required divine intervention.
Madam, when you brought your son to The SCOAN and he received prayer;
can you just tell us what happened and what are the changes that you saw in his life thereafter?
Praise the Lord!
When we came to The SCOAN, my son was placed at the prayer line.
During the prayer, he fainted and I knew that something had happened.
On reaching home, after six days, everything became normal.
Praise the Lord!
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time.
Thank You, Jesus Christ!
We give all the glory to God.
Madam, in the lights of what God has done for your son, what is your own word of advice for our viewers?
Praise the Lord!
Parents, I want you to take note of your children.
Observe their movements; observe the type of friends they keep.
You may not follow them everywhere they go but you can render prayers.
I took a bold step believing that I have a God who would answer and deliver him.
Inside me, I felt that the operation was not going to be successful.
So, I want to address mothers especially.
Mothers, say "Praise the Lord!"
Mothers have a lot to do.
Men are often too busy.
As a mother, it is your duty to do good work.
Your husband is just like a baby in your hands - I always say this.
Especially your children, they are little babies, no matter how they have grown.
You have to decide for them in some issues, especially in terms of spiritual battle.
So, I believe that if we follow these tips, God will see us through, in Jesus' name.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Finally, let's hear a word from the father of the young man as well.
Sir, you are welcome.
Please, introduce yourself to us and tell us what can you say about this wonderful testimony.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Anthony Dennis Kachiro.
We are all from Kaduna State.
He is Victor Kachiro, my fourth son,
and this is my darling; wife Rebecca Kachiro.
The devil wanted to enter the family but with the faith that my wife had, we were able to succeed.
It was one morning, when I was preparing to go to work for an assignment
that I received a phone call that my son had been taken to the general hospital.
I tried to ask them what the matter was because I hadn't had any reported case of ill health.
Then, the person who tried to tell me said that it was something very strange.
I became so confused and told my wife to rush to the hospital.
She went after analysing and seeing everything and then called me on the phone,
and told me that they were talking about an operation.
I reminded her that she had told me he was in serious pain
and asked her what she wanted us to do, that why couldn't she just allow them to operate
but she insisted that he had to be taken for prayers in The SCOAN.
So, I accepted.
I have to thank God for making this possible.
She came and we made arrangements.
That is exactly what has happened.
I want to say that she has encouraged me and encouraged the family
because we were all confused at that stage.
So, once again, we can understand how critical the situation was.
Glory be to God that your son came to The SCOAN.
Sir, what can you say about the transformation in his life through the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua?
There was a transformation, not only concerning the sickness
but also concerning some of the issues we were confronting.
As soon as he was prayed for, when he received his healing,
he became strong and everything was so much in order.
There were some things that some of his brothers could not do that he, wholeheartedly,
had engaged himself in doing – all those things that we had been missing from a son.
Amen.
So, you mean to say he was completely restored, the permanent erection went after the prayer,
he has now been living a normal life for several months?
Yes.
Exactly, glory be to God.
Finally sir, what is your own word of advice?
I want to advise all youth that they should always try to follow things gradually.
Going into these vices of smoking, drinking and doing what they are not supposed to do will not help them.
Rather, they are to hold fast to their studies so they would be able to achieve and build a family.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!